fadavis.com 2010-12-30

# F.A. Davis Company® - Privacy Policy

F.A. Davis is  committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to collect and ship orders.  Please read on for more details about our privacy policy. 

What information do we collect? How do we use it? 

  * When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. 
  * When you sign up for our New Release Service, we need only an e-mail address--which we use to send the information you requested. 
  * When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners. 
  * When you register as a Faculty Member on FADavis.com   your registration information (i.e., your e-mail address and nickname)  will not disclose your information, and your information will remain fully protected by FADavis.com's privacy policy. 
  * Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to **** notify you about important functionality changes to the Website, new FADavis.com services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. I 

**How does F.A. Davis.com protect customer information?**   
When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.  F.A. Davis.com does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. 

**In summary**  
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make shopping at F.A. Davis.com possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We may choose to do so in the future with trustworthy third parties, but you can tell us not to by sending a blank e-mail message to [remove@F.A. Davis.com](mailto:never@fadavis.com). 

**Your consent**   
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by F.A. Davis.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

F.A. Davis is not responsible for the privacy policies of Web sites to which this site may link.
